janglo.net 2018-02-02

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Janglo (“the Site”) respects the privacy of our users and members. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information that we collect and the uses that we make of that information. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

In order to enhance your experience on our site we may collect certain information about you.  This information may be information provided by you, (for example, information that you provide to us such as your name or your email address) or information gathered through your use of our website or through 3rd parties (for example, The IP address of your computer, Web pages and/or ads that you view or click on) 

WHAT WE DO WITH INFORMATION WE GATHER 

We use information that we collect and/or have access to via reputable 3rd parties in order to enhance your experience while visiting our site.  Information we gather is used for: 

A: CONTENT AND SERVICES 

We may use information we collect to better understand your needs and provide you with a better online experience and to customize the information and content we show you. For example: 

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services and provide you with customized content. 

  * We may use your email address, provided username and/or password in order to grant you access to premium services on our site 

  * Serving content based on selected preferences you have chosen or you geographic location, age or gender 

B: ADVERTISING 

Our site offers advertising and other services which helps us fund our site’s operation.  We strive to offer high quality advertisements and promotions that we think will be of interest to you and to our visitors.  These ads may be in the form of banner ads and or other promotional services offered on our website or on our opt-in email list 

We may use user information that is either provided by you or gathered with the use of cookies and similar technologies as well as information provided by reputable 3rd party data providers to better understand your needs and provide you with a better online experience and to customize the ads we show you. For example: 

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about products, special offers or other information that we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 

  * We may use information you provide us or that is collected by us or collected by 3rd parties to show you advertising and ads that we think might appeal to you.  These ads might be targeted and shown to you on the basis of such things as your gender, age, geographic location, web sites you visit and other information. 

HOW WE USE COOKIES 

In order to improve our ability to predict which ads We, our third party service providers, advertisers or our partners may use "cookies" or similar technologies, to monitor our visitors surfing patterns and preferences and collect other data about the visitors using our site. 

We may use cookies or similar technologies to monitor and measure traffic and to customize the content. We also may use cookies to collect information about you and your preferences  which helps us offer you products, promotions, or services that may be of interest to you and to deliver relevant advertising tailored to you. 

We may also use the services of third parties to provide us with data collection to assist with delivery of relevant banners and advertisements. This data may include information like demographic data, such as age range, gender, and interests 

HOW YOU MAY LIMIT OR BLOCK COOKIES 

You can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or even to block all cookies (although blocking all cookies may diminish some of the services we can offer you including providing you with tailored advertising) 

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers. websites. Alternatively, you may use the resources located at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices> to opt out 

Many third-party advertising networks are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"). To opt out of having information collected by NAI member companies used for behavioral advertising, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>. 

You may also opt out of cookies by “Opting out” of a particular 3rd party provider.  For example, to opt out of cookies placed by the Zedo Ad server , [go to the Zedo Opt Out page](http://out/) and click the “Opt Out Now” 

E-Mail:   
Using the e-mail addresses provided during registrations, surveys, and contests, we may, periodically, send promotional e-mail to our subscribers about services offered by us, and by carefully selected advertisers. If you do not wish to receive solicitations sent on behalf of third parties, you may unsubscribe at any time. 

Security:  
Although we take precautions against security breaches, hackers pose a threat to any Internet user. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to see that your information is treated in compliance with this privacy policy.
